[CHANTS]
One of us, one of us.
(Penny:)Well, what a thrill.
- You're sitting in my spot.
- Oh, gee, you've gotta be kidding me.
- Leonard, she's in my spot.
- Yeah, yeah.
(Leonard:)See, here's the thing...
(Leonard:)...after you leave,
I still have to live with him.
(Penny:)I don't care. I'm taking a stand.
(Penny:)Metaphorically.
(Sheldon:)All right, that's it.
(Sheldon:)- Strike three.
- Oh, strike three.
(Penny:)I'm banished?
(Penny:)- What the hell kind of crap is that?
LEONARD: Listen.
(Leonard:)- Don't worry, I'll talk to him.
- Yeah, you do that.
(Leonard:)Just so I know,
would you be open to taking his class?
(Leonard:)You can do it online.
So on our triangulation, we've narrowed
the location of the Top Model house...
(Howard:)...to three square miles
in the Hollywood Hills.
(Raj:)Or possibly Durham, North Carolina.